jestro.com 2019-09-25

# The Theme Foundry – WordPress themes for publishers

Your privacy is critically important to us. At The Theme Foundry we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

It is The Theme Foundry’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, The Theme Foundry collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The Theme Foundry’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how The Theme Foundry’s visitors use its website. From time to time, The Theme Foundry may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

The Theme Foundry also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blog. The Theme Foundry only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to The Theme Foundry’s websites choose to interact with The Theme Foundry in ways that require The Theme Foundry to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that The Theme Foundry gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who purchase a product at thethemefoundry.com to provide their name, a username, and an email address. We also record the referring site and / or advertising campaign of the purchaser if available. The Theme Foundry collects such information and only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with The Theme Foundry. The Theme Foundry does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information or ask to have their personally-identifying information deleted, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

The Theme Foundry may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. The Theme Foundry may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, The Theme Foundry does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

The Theme Foundry discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on The Theme Foundry’s behalf or to provide services available at The Theme Foundry’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using The Theme Foundry’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. The Theme Foundry will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, The Theme Foundry discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when The Theme Foundry believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of The Theme Foundry, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of The Theme Foundry website and have supplied your email address, The Theme Foundry may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with The Theme Foundry and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. The Theme Foundry takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitors computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Theme Foundry uses cookies to help The Theme Foundry identify and track visitors, their usage of The Theme Foundry website, and their website access preferences. The Theme Foundry visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using The Theme Foundry’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of The Theme Foundry’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If The Theme Foundry, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that The Theme Foundry goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of The Theme Foundry may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, The Theme Foundry may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in The Theme Foundry’s sole discretion. The Theme Foundry encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This Privacy Policy was crafted from [Automattic’s version](http://automattic.com/privacy/), which is available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.
